Guide to the Stephen M. Cabrinety Collection in the History of Microcomputing, ca. 1975-1995
Department of Special Collections
- Software, Series 1
  - Utilities software, Subseries 1.7
    - Microdeal Electronic Publishing Digi-Drum from 2-Bit systems, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 146)
    - Microillusions Photon Paint, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 42)
    - Microsoft Corporation Microsoft BASIC Interpreter, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 51)
    - Microsoft Corporation Microsoft BASIC Interpreter 2.1, n.d., Macintosh (Box 106)
    - Microsoft Corporation Microsoft Chart, 1984, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 51)
    - Microsoft Corporation Microsoft File data management program, 1985, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 52)
    - Microsoft Corporation Microsoft Sort, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. MS-DOS (Box 66)
    - Miles Computing Inc. Mac the Knife volume 6: Taking care of business, 1989, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 109)
    - Miles Computing Inc Quintette, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - Mindscape, Inc. The Luescher [Lüscher] Profile: know your own personality, 1985, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Apple (Box 6)
    - Mindscape, Inc. The Perfect College, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 112)
    - Moon Valley Software Do it on your desktop!, 1993, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Windows (Box 1)
    - Most Significant Bits Windows Heaven, 1993, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Windows (Box 40)
    - MST Incorporated School House: 30 educational programs, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 173)
    - Oakwood Publishing Jr. Desk, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 65)
    - Oakwood Publishing Jr. File, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 65)
    - Olduvai Software, Inc. Just Icon It!, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 49)
    - Optimized Systems Software Inc DOS XL: includes BUG/65, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 83)
    - Optimized Systems Software Inc Personal Pascal, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 76)
    - Origin Systems Inc. Moebius by Greg Malone, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Apple (Box 120)
    - PAR Software, Inc. DiskPro +!, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Amiga (Box 41)
    - Paragon Software Corporation Twilight: 2000, 1994, 5 computer disk; 3 ½ in. MS-DOS (Box 19)
    - Paramount Interactive Rock Rap 'n Roll, 1993, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Windows (Box 171)
    - Parsons Technology, Inc. Personal Tax Edge: 1992 Final Filing Version- Installation Disc 1, 1993, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. MS-DOS (Box 3)
    - PBI Software Jeeves: The affordable personal assistant, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 114)
    - PC SIG, Inc. Shareware Breakthrough: Utilities and Productivity Collection, 1993, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 175)
    - Penguin Software, Inc. Cat Graphics, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 125)
    - Penguin Software, Inc. Paper Graphics, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple; Atari (Box 123)
    - Penguin Software, Inc. Transitions: a presentation system by Andre Schklowsky, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 122)
    - Peter Norton Computing, Inc. Norton Utilities Version 3.1, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 66)
    - Pinpoint KeyPlayer, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.Apple (Box 116)
    - Pinpoint Publishing Pinpoint, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 125)
    - Pitney Bowes, Inc. DATA Long term Acctg., 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 95)
    - Pitney Bowes, Inc. Rates / Zip-to-Zone, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 95)
    - Pitney Bowes, Inc. Rates / Zip-to-Zone Program disk Version 1.01C, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 95)
    - Pitney Bowes, Inc. Transaction Disk, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 95)
    - Pitney Bowes, Inc. Utility disc, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 95)
    - PLUG, The Plus/4 User's Group Tools / Finance, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 203)
    - Polarware Map Pack, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 107)
    - Practicorp International, Inc. 64 Doctor, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - Professional Software, Inc. Fleet System 3, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 105)
    - Professional Software, Inc. Fleet System 3, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - Professional Software, Inc. Lotus Alphabytes: classic atlas metro, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 106)
    - Program Design, Inc. The Alphabet Arcade, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 117)
    - Progressive Peripherals & Software Apple CPA Free Running Demo, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 112)
    - Quantum Axcess Cyberdelic screen savers for Windows, n.d., computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Windows (Box 24)
    - Quark, Incorporated Catalyst Program Selector, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 44)
    - Quark, Incorporated Quark Catalyst IIe, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 44)
    - Real Software, Inc. Computer Diagnostics, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 28)
    - Real Software Inc Disk Utilities, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 61)
    - Real Software Inc Disk Utilities, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 61)
    - Reality Technologies Business Week's Business Advantage: Business Simulation Software, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.Macintosh (Box 107)
    - Rocklan Software Tele Com, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 147)
    - Samna Corporation Samna Word IV.--Rev. 1.0, 1986, 12 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 95)
    - Scarborough Systems, Inc. The Scarborough System: MasterType's Writer by Learning Ways, Inc., n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 182)
    - Second Nature Software Inc Slide Show Sampler: Screen Saver and Wallpaper for Windows, 1993, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Windows (Box 20)
    - Shanner International Corporation MacroManager, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 144)
    - Shanner International Corporation MacroManager, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 144)
    - Share Data, Inc. Computing Tools, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Sharedata Graphics Master, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 117)
    - Sharedata Graphics Master, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 176)
    - Sherburne Knowledge Systems Shareware Gold II: The Golden ROM Series, 1991, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 175)
    - Sierra On-Line Homeword: The Personal Word Processor, 1983, 3 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 21)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Home Word Plus, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 110)
    - Sight & Sound Music Software, Inc. Music Processor, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 179)
    - Sight & Sound Music Software, Inc. Music Video Hits, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 179)
    - Sight & Sound Music Software, Inc. Music Video Kit, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 179)
    - Sight & Sound Music Software, Inc. On Stage, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 179)
    - Silicon Beach Software, Inc. Silicon Press, 1985, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 52)
    - Sm Software Inc Gnome Speed: BASIC 7.0 compiler, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Softdisk, Inc. Chameleon, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - SoftKey Software Products of Florida, Inc. More Key Fonts for Windows, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Windows (Box 2)
    - Softsmith Software List Master, 1982, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 113)
    - Southwest Data Systems, Inc. Merlin: A Macro Assembler for the Apple II, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 125)
    - Southwestern Data Systems CopyCat, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 44)
    - Southwestern Data Systems Merlin: macro assembler for the Apple II (2 copies), c. 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 48)
    - Southwestern Data Systems & Sampler I, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - Southwestern Data Systems & Screen, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - Spinnaker Software Spreadsheet, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 184)
    - Stac Electronics Stacker for Windows and DOS, 1994, ? computer disk; 3 ½ in. Windows (Box 3)
    - Strategic Simulations, Inc. Speed Demon high octane apple juice, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 144)
    - Sublogic Co. 3-D Graphic transform Applesoft II ROM, 1979, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 120)
    - Suncom Animation Station shape library 1, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 108)
    - Suncom Mac Font 1, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 110)
    - Supersoft "Tiny" Pascal, 1979, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 93)
    - Survivor Software, Ltd. MacMoney: Accounting and financial planning for the Macintosh, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 115)
    - Swift Word Processor, 1988, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 164)
    - Swift Professional Paint Plus: multiple layer graphics system, 1992, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 166)
    - Synapse Prototype Tutorial Synapse Synfile+, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 155)
    - Synapse Software Inc FileManager 800+, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 85)
    - Synergistic Software Directory Manager, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple; Atari (Box 123)
    - Synergistic Software Program Line Editor, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple; Atari (Box 123)
    - Systems Software, Ltd. The Ultimate Utility Package: Hack-Pack, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 187)
    - T & F Software Co. Secur-a-text, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - Tandy, Corp. Color Scripsit II, 1986, 1 computer cartridgeTRS-80 (Box 95)
    - Terrific Software Print 'n' Draw: exciting applications programs for the Atari 1020 Printer Plotter: 40 column text editor, banner, picture, & pie chard generator by Bill Williams, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 95)
    - The Alien Group When I'm 64, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 148)
    - The Software Toolworks Backup Pro, 1989, computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 13)
    - Timeworks Inc Partner PC, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 67)
    - Timeworks, Inc. Programming Kit 1: beginning game design, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 183)
    - Timeworks, Inc. Programming Kit 2: intermediate game design and sprite builder, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 183)
    - Timeworks, Inc. Swiftax (1986), 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 128)
    - Titan Technologies, Inc. VC-Expand/80.--universal version, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 57)
    - Trilobyte The Money Manager, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 21)
    - Tronix S.A.M. The Software Automatic Mouth, 1982, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 124)
    - Tronix S.A.M. The Software Automatic Mouth, 1982, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 199)
    - Unison World Print Master Plus, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 110)
    - Unison World PrintMaster Art Gallery II, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 144)
    - Unison World PrintMaster Plus, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 144)
    - Unison World Incorporated PrintMaster Art Gallery I, 1985, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 42)
    - United Software Security Inc Privacy Plus, n.d., DOS (Othertype 67)
    - Unknown Disk # 1 Graphics & Music, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 219)
    - Unknown DOS 2.1, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 95)
    - Unknown IBM [?] Boot disk, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in.DOS (Box 95)
    - Wayzata Technology CardShop Plus! for Windows, 1994, 1 computer optical discs; 4 3/4 in. computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Windows (Box 1)
    - Wayzata Technology CD-ROM explorer pack [interactive multimedia]: a collection of ten full-length CD-ROMs, 1994, 10 computer optical discs; 4 3/4 in. computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Windows (Box 1)
    - Wayzata Technology CD-ROM treasure pack I [computer file]: a collection of ten full-length CD-ROM gems, 1994, 10 computer optical discs; 4 3/4 in. + 1 Font pro guide. computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Windows (Box 1)
    - Wayzata Technology Tony Quinn's virtual galaxy [interactive multimedia]. CD-ROM explorer pack; pt. 1, [no. 1], 1994, 1 computer optical discs; 4 3/4 in. computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Windows (Box 1)
    - Wizardware Multimedia, Ltd. CD-Rom Desktop Magic color clip-art and graphics viewing program, n.d., 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 166)
    - Working Software Inc. Lookup, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Macintosh (Box 50)
- Hardware, Series 2
  - 3-M Remote Diagnostic Systemn.d., Model No. 103JLP; Item No. 00360 (Box 60)
  - A.T.&T. Cables and mouse for Vic-20n.d., Item No. 00368
  - A.T.&T. Monitorn.d., Model No. CRT-313-B; Item No. 00236 (Box 2)
  - A.T.&T. Unix PCn.d., Model No. PC7300; Item No. 00388
  - Advanced Interface Devices, Inc. R-Verter Serial Bus Modem Adaptor1984, Item No. 00091 (Box 2)
  - AMP 25-pin serial I/O cablen.d., Item No. 00300 (Box 34)
  - Anchor Automation, Inc. Volks Mini 1200/ 300 BPS Modemn.d., Item No. 00023 (Box 10)
  - Anchor Automation, Inc. Volks Mini 1200/ 300 BPS Modemn.d., Item No. 00338 (Box 10)
  - Anchor Automation, Inc. Volks Mini 1200/ 300 BPS Modemn.d., Item No. 00406 (Box 69)
  - Anchor Automation, Inc. Volksmodem 12n.d., Model No. VM12; Item No. 00112 (Box 55)
  - Anderson Jacobson Inc. Acoustic Data Coupler 1980, Model No. A242A; Item No. 00050 (Box 22)
  - Anderson Jacobson Inc. Acoustic Data Couplern.d., Model No. A-242A; Item No. 00142 (Box 51)
  - Anko Joystickn.d., Item No. 00408 (Box 70)
  - APF Electronics, Inc. TV Funn.d., Model No. 401A; Item No. 00066 (Box 60)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple Adjustable Keyboard1992, Model No. M1242; Item No. 00187 (Box 35)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple Color RGB Monitor [for Apple IIGS]1987 May, Model No. A2M6014; Item No. 00073 (Box 77)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple Desktop Bus keyboardn.d., Model No. A9M0330; Item No. 00124 (Box 53)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple extended keyboard II1990, Model No. M3501; Item No. 00126 (Box 62)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple II Disk II drive n.d., Model No. A2M0003; Item No. 00071 (Box 62)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple II GS computern.d. [ca. 1987], Model No. A2S60000; Item No. 00074 (Box 69)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple II Plus computer[1979], Model No. A2S1016; Item No. 00070 (Box 87)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple IIe computern.d., Model No. A2S2064; Item No. 00076 (Box 68)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple IIe computern.d., Model No. A2S1048; Item No. 00270 (Box 68)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple keyboard1990, Model No. 658-4081; Item No. 00125 (Box 53)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple keyboardn.d., Model No. M0116; Item No. 00127 (Box 18)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple Macintosh 3 ½ in. Drive 1986, Model No. A9M0106; Item No. 00202 (Box 11)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Apple Macintosh SE1986, Model No. M5011; Item No. 00201 (Box 11)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. External 3 ½ in. floppy disk driven.d., Model No. M0130; Item No. 00144 (Box 57)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Floppy drive; 3 ½ in.n.d., Model No. OA-D34V-01; Item No. 00165 (Box 50)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Image Writer IIn.d., Model No. A9M0310; Item No. 00212 (Box 80)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Macintosh 3 ½ in. floppy disk drive1984, Model No. M0130; Item No. 00253 (Box 61)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Macintosh 512K computer1984, Model No. M0001W; Item No. 00251 (Box 26)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Macintosh 512K computer keyboard1984, Model No. M0110; Item No. 00252 (Box 3)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Monitor III1982 Nov., Model No. A3M0039; Item No. 00218 (Box 12)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Monitor III1982 Nov., Model No. A3M0039; Item No. 00269 (Box 24)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Mouse for Macintosh 1984, Model No. M0100; Item No. 00256 (Box 7)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Printern.d., Model No. A9M0303; Item No. 00255 (Box 28)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Printern.d., Model No. A9M0303; Item No. 00261 (Box 22)
  - Apple Computer, Inc. Silentype Printern.d., Model No. A2M0032; Item No. 00059 (Box 4)
  - Applied Engineering Transwarp Accellerator Card for Apple II or IIe1985, Model No. 1.3; Item No. 00081 (Box 24)
  - Atari Atari 2600n.d., Model No. A3M0039; Item No. 00423 (Box 12)
  - Atari Atari 65XE Personal Computer1984, Item No. 00416 (Box 90)
  - Atari Atari Touch Tablet with AtariArtist software1988, Model No. VT100AA; Item No. 00414 (Box 88)
  - Atari SX212 Modem1988, Model No. VT100AA; Item No. 00413 (Box 88)
  - Atari, Inc. 2 driving controllersn.d., Item No. 00275 (Box 34)
  - Atari, Inc. 2 sets paddle controllersn.d., Item No. 00273 (Box 52)
  - Atari, Inc. 3 AC Power Adaptersn.d., Model No. AC95000; Item No. 00279 (Box 52)
  - Atari, Inc. 3 ac power supply modulesn.d., Item No. 00294 (Box 54)
  - Atari, Inc. 4 Joysticksn.d., Item No. 00276 (Box 33)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 1010 cassette playern.d., Model No. 1010; Item No. 00030 (Box 8)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 1040STn.d., Model No. 1040STFM; Item No. 00026 (Box 63)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 1050 5 ¼ in. floppy Disk Driven.d., Model No. 1050; Item No. 00025 (Box 11)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 1050 5 ¼ in. floppy disk driven.d., Model No. 1050; Item No. 00031 (Box 24)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 1050 5 ¼ in. floppy disk driven.d., Model No. 1050; Item No. 00128 (Box 59)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 1050 5 ¼ in. floppy disk driven.d., Model No. 1050; Item No. 00129 (Box 59)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 1050 5 ¼ in. floppy disk Driven.d., Model No. 1050; Item No. 00148 (Box 55)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 1050 5 ¼ in. floppy disk Driven.d., Model No. 1050; Item No. 00149 (Box 56)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 2600n.d., Model No. CX-2600 A; Item No. 00034 (Box 26)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 2600 game systemn.d., Item No. 00147 (Box 59)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 2600 Remote Control Wireless Joysticks [2 copies]n.d., Item No. 00340 (Box 3)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 400 personal computern.d., Model No. 400; Item No. 00109 (Box 49)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 600XL Home Computern.d., Item No. 00019 (Box 25)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 65XE personal computern.d., Model No. 65XE; Item No. 00143 (Box 58)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 7800 ProSystemn.d., Model No. Atari 7800; Item No. 00056 (Box 5)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 800n.d., Model No. 800-093; Item No. 00021 (Box 22)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 800 Personal Computern.d., Model No. Atari 800; Item No. 00405 (Box 80)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 800XL Personal Computern.d., Model No. 800XL; Item No. 00135 (Box 45)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 800XL Personal Computern.d., Model No. 800XL; Item No. 00136 (Box 53)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 810 5 ¼ in. floppy disk driven.d., Model No. 810; Item No. 00130 (Box 57)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari 810 5 ¼ in. floppy disk driven.d., Model No. 810; Item No. 00131 (Box 43)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari Numerical Keyboard1982, Model No. CX85; Item No. 00084 (Box 8)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari Plug-In Power Supplyn.d., Model No. C016353; Item No. 00037 (Box 1)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari power supplyn.d., Model No. CO61982; Item No. 00033 (Box 1)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari Power Supplyn.d., Model No. C016353; Item No. 00036 (Box 3)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari Power Supplyn.d., Model No. CO61982; Item No. 00133 (Box 57)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari Power Supplyn.d., Model No. CO61982; Item No. 00134 (Box 47)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari Program Recordern.d., Model No. 410; Item No. 00107 (Box 41)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari Program Recordern.d., Model No. 410; Item No. 00114 (Box 43)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari Program Recordern.d., Model No. 410; Item No. 00132 (Box 46)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari SC1224 Monitor1985 Aug., Model No. SC1224; Item No. 00028 (Box 73)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari STM1 mousen.d., Model No. STM1; Item No. 00027 (Box 72)
  - Atari, Inc. Atari Video Pinballn.d., Model No. C-380; Item No. 00035 (Box 8)
  - Atari, Inc. Bookkeeper kitn.d., Item No. 00395 (Box 66)
  - Atari, Inc. Computer cablen.d., Item No. 00312 (Box 10)
  - Atari, Inc. Monitor1985 June, Model No. SM124; Item No. 00196 (Box 14)
  - Atari, Inc. Paddle controller setn.d., Item No. 00407 (Box 72)
  - Atari, Inc. Power supplyn.d., Model No. c016353; Item No. 00409 (Box 72)
  - Atari, Inc. Sears Video Arcade IIn.d., Model No. 637.75000; Item No. 00017 (Box 23)
  - Atari, Inc. Stunt Cyclen.d., Model No. SC-450; Item No. 00068 (Box 60)
  - Atari, Inc. Tele-Games Hockey Pongn.d., Model No. 637.99721; Item No. 00046 (Box 25)
  - Atari, Inc. Tele-Games Video Arcaden.d., Model No. 637.99743; Item No. 00151 (Box 56)
  - Atari, Inc. Trak-Ball Controller1983, Model No. CX22; Item No. 00092 (Box 62)
  - Atari, Inc. Video Computer Systemn.d., Model No. CX-2600; Item No. 00145 (Box 42)
  - Atari, Inc. Video Computer Systemn.d., Model No. CX-2600; Item No. 00146 (Box 41)
  - Atari, Inc. Video computer systemn.d., Model No. 2600; Item No. 00156 (Box 36)
  - Atari, Inc. Video computer systemn.d., Model No. 2600; Item No. 00181 (Box 36)
  - Atari, Inc. Video Computer Systemn.d., Model No. CX-2600; Item No. 00198 (Box 63)
  - Atari, Inc. Video Computer Systemn.d., Model No. CX-2600; Item No. 00245
  - Atari, Inc. Video Touch Padn.d., Item No. 00264 (Box 7)
  - Bally Arcade Control Handlesn.d., Model No. ACI-0200; Item No. 00351 (Box 7)
  - Beeshu Jazz Stickn.d., Item No. 00417 (Box 89)
  - Beeshu, Inc. Ultimate Superstick joystick1988, Item No. 00330
  - BMC International Solid State Monitor1982 Feb., Model No. BM-12AU; Item No. 00213 (Box 17)
  - BMC USA, Inc. Monitor [for Apple IIe]1984 Sept., Model No. JJ-1201G; Item No. 00075 (Box 29)
  - Bondwell Global, Ltd. Quickshot Flightgrip 2 Joystick1990, Item No. 00336 (Box 24)
  - Bondwell Global, Ltd. Quickshot Python 3 Joystick1991, Item No. 00319 (Box 7)
  - Botek Instruments CCP-1 Serial Interfacen.d., Item No. 00321 (Box 13)
  - Businessland, Inc. Monitorn.d., Model No. KI542-074I; Item No. 00197
  - Cardco, Inc. Card? Cardprint +G Printer interface for Commodore 64/ VIC-201985, Item No. 00311 (Box 13)
  - Casio Computer Co., Ltd. PT-100 Electronic Musical Instrumentn.d., Model No. 800-093; Item No. 00022 (Box 70)
  - Chicony Electronics Co., Ltd. Keyboardn.d., Model No. KB-5191; Item No. 00382 (Box 63)
  - Coleco Industries, Inc. ADAMn.d., Model No. 2410CPU; Item No. 00063 (Box 67)
  - Coleco Industries, Inc. Adam central processing unitn.d., Model No. 2410CPU; Item No. 00259 (Box 69)
  - Coleco Industries, Inc. Adam Keyboardn.d., Model No. 2410KB; Item No. 00258 (Box 62)
  - Coleco Industries, Inc. Adam Smartwriter Printern.d., Model No. 41021; Item No. 00257 (Box 25)
  - Coleco Industries, Inc. Adam television switchboxn.d., Item No. 00376 (Box 32)
  - Coleco Industries, Inc. Adam, the Colecovision Family computer systemn.d., Model No. 2410CPU; Item No. 00373 (Box 69)
  - Coleco Industries, Inc. Adam, the Colecovision Family computer system controllersn.d., Item No. 00375 (Box 31)
  - Coleco Industries, Inc. Adam, the Colecovision Family computer system keyboardn.d., Model No. 2410KB; Item No. 00374
  - Coleco Industries, Inc. Adam, the Colecovision Family computer system Smartwriter printer n.d., Model No. 72559; Item No. 00377 (Box 77)
  - Coleco Industries, Inc. Kid Vid Voice Module for Atari 2600n.d., Item No. 00337 (Box 1)
  - Coleco Industries, Inc. My Talking Computern.d., Item No. 00326 (Box 11)
  - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. 1530 Datassette Unitn.d., Model No. C2N-B; Item No. 00365 (Box 21)
  - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. 1530 Datassette Unit, Model C2N1983, Item No. 00005 (Box 7)
  - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. 1531 Datassetten.d., Model No. 1531; Item No. 00174 (Box 44)
  - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. 1531 Datassetten.d., Model No. 1531; Item No. 00175 (Box 44)
  - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. 2 AC power supplyn.d., Item No. 00292 (Box 34)
  - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. 5 ¼ in. floppy disk driven.d., Model No. 1541; Item No. 00155